https://www.ocra.com/privacy-policy

Home/ Privacy Policy & Use of OCRA Website
OCRA Worldwide provides this Privacy Policy to describe our privacy practices relating to persons who are not our clients and the choices such persons can make about the way personal information is collected and how that information is used. This Privacy Policy applies to:
Visitors to our websites, who interact with our websites in any way (including by the completion of online forms, sending us email).
Persons who communicate with OCRA Worldwide by any other method (such as by telephone, facsimile or letter)
This Privacy Policy ceases to apply when persons contract with us and become our clients as our terms relating to client privacy and confidentiality are contained in our Terms of Business. Clients should note that the privacy and confidentiality provisions in our Terms of Business differ from this Privacy Policy.
Sites covered by this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to www.ocra.com.
Links to Non-OCRA Worldwide Websites
The OCRA Worldwide Websites may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave our websites. OCRA Worldwide does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from OCRA Worldwide’s. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. OCRA Worldwide’s Privacy Policy does not cover the personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information.
Browsing OCRA Worldwide Websites
If you visit any OCRA Worldwide Website and do not complete any online forms or communicate with us in any other way, you should note that: We will not collect or retain any personal data from you in this case.
Our servers will seek to place a cookie on your computer so that we may track statistics relating to visitors which cannot be used to identify individuals. Please click here for more information about our cookie policy.
How we treat your personal information
If you complete an online form or communicate with us by any means, Members of OCRA Worldwide will collect personal data from you, will communicate with you and use this personal data to facilitate supplying services and products.
This may mean that personal data is passed to firms and organisations that are not members of OCRA Worldwide for the purposes relating to supplying our services such as shipping services and other third party service providers acting upon our request to fulfil your requests.
OCRA Worldwide may utilise personal data to provide reference notes, guidelines, advice and for marketing such other services and products and providing such other information as Members of OCRA Worldwide may from time to time make available. If you do not wish to receive this type of information, you should advise us by contacting privacy@ocra.com
Categories of personal data we collect
We collect the following personal data about you:
Your name and contact details such as email address, telephone number, fax number as provided by you in the online forms.
Identity information such as Passport number, Date of birth, Place of Birth, Nationality – information which may be required to facilitate supplying services to you.
Keeping your personal information secure
OCRA Worldwide is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, OCRA Worldwide has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.
Data Retention
We will only keep your personal data for as long as we are obliged by the law to do so.
Your Rights
Under applicable data protection laws, you may have the right in certain cases :
to request access to your personal data that we process
to request details about such personal data including the purposes and any recipients of this data
to have such personal data updated or deleted
to have the processing of personal data restricted
to request a copy of your personal data in a standardized format.
The most effective way to obtain information or change any personal information we may collect is to contact privacy@ocra.com. . Prior to making changes to personal data or releasing information we will confirm that email requests to privacy@ocra.com are genuine by comparing the information contained in email requests against our records and seeking confirmation by email to the email address we hold on record or by seeking written instructions.
Sharing or disclosing personal information
The personal information and personal data we collect is used only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and in this manner, it is never sold, lent or leased to third parties. Members of OCRA Worldwide reserve the right to treat these obligations of privacy as not applicable when obliged by law.
Distribution of Personal Information outside the EEA
As some Members of OCRA Worldwide are outside the EEA and as the provision of services and products by Members of OCRA Worldwide may necessitate the transfer of personal data and personal information outside the EEA, users and potential clients must accept that this may mean that personal data may be transferred to countries that do not provide adequate protection of data in accordance with the GDPR.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If there are updates to the terms of our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes and update the revision date on this website, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have. Prior to changing our Privacy Policy to allow new unrelated uses of your personal data we will post a notice on our home page advising that our Privacy Policy will be changing in 30 days and send you an email so that you may choose not to accept these new unrelated uses of your personal data.
Contacting Us
We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send them to the privacy@ocra.com.
Type your search
Search
EuropeUnited Kingdom
+44 (20) 7317 0600
enquiry@ocra.co.uk
Visit website
Luxembourg
+352 224 286
Contact Number
What date would be convenient to call you?
What time would you like to be called?
00h00
01h00
02h00
03h00
04h00
05h00
06h00
07h00
(GMT -9:00) Alaska
(GMT -8:00) Pacific Time (US & Canada)
(GMT -7:00) Mountain Time (US & Canada)
(GMT -6:00) Central Time (US & Canada), Mexico City
(GMT -5:00) Eastern Time (US & Canada), Bogota, Lima
(GMT -4:00) Atlantic Time (Canada), Caracas, La Paz
(GMT -3:30) Newfoundland
(GMT -3:00) Brazil, Buenos Aires, Georgetown
(GMT -2:00) Mid-Atlantic
(GMT -1:00 hour) Azores, Cape Verde Islands
(GMT) Western Europe Time, London, Lisbon, Casablanca
Email
Select the office to which you would like to direct your enquiry
Select the office to which you would like to direct your enquiry...
Hong Kong
Mauritius
Singapore
Shanghai
Seychelles
Madeira
I am not sure which office to direct my enquiry to. Please advise.
Message
reCAPTCHA
OCRA Worldwide respects your privacy. Your details will never be disclosed to any third party for any purpose without your prior written consent.
Consent
I give consent for the personal data provided in this form to be used by the OCRA Worldwide office specified above or any OCRA office, to contact me for my free consultation.
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
